[i]The Seven Sins. They had battled and bloodied one another, they had kept secrets, broken hearts, lied, betrayed, exiled, they had walked away, said goodbye and sworn it was forever, and somehow, every time, they had mended, they had forgiven, they had survived. Some mistakes could never be fixed - some, but not all. Some people can't be driven away, no matter how hard you try. Some friendships won't break.
― Robin Wasserman[/i]
*page_break Prologue

[i]The seperation of Heaven and Hell, many know the story.[/i]
*line_break
[i]God was betrayed by his closest friend and confidant, Lucifer[/i]
*line_break
[i]And thusly Lucifer was banished down to the pits of hell, where he was rumored to have created the seven sins that plague humaity.[/i]
*line_break
[i]These seven beings stood alongside Lucifer ruling the eight kingdoms of Hell.[/i]
*line_break
[i]Where they would torment the souls of the dammned and wage war against Heaven itself.[/i]
*line_break
[i]This soon became known to many throughout the years and time as the Great Divide of Heaven and Hell[/i]
*line_break
[i]However...[/i]
*page_break This story is wrong....

[i]The seperation was caused by nessesity.[/i]
*line_break
[i]There was no great betrayal.[/i]
*line_break
[i]There was no war waged.[/i]
*line_break
[i]And most importantly the sins came about on their own.[/i]
*line_break
[i]Previously known as the seven virtues of Heaven,they became the seven sins of humanity.[/i]
*line_break
[i]For one to keep a proper balance sacrifices must be made.[/i]
*page_break Chapter 1



